Guide to the Jen Stone WTO Seattle Protests Collection
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Jen Stone WTO Seattle Protests collection
1999-2003
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
6225
6225-001
Stone, Jen
1.59 cubic feet 2 boxes plus 1 oversize folder
Documents and videos on the Seattle World Trade Organization protests, and other labor-related events
Materials include assorted mini-DV tapes and VHS tapes of footage from the protests, including interviews conducted by the donor, as well as other recordings from IndyMedia and others. Collection also contains an oversized poster, local newspaper publications from 1999 and 2000 about protest, and files with correspondence between donor and others, newsletters, reports, and flyers.
Contact repository for access to audiovisual material.
No restrictions on access.
Jen Stone (Dormeier)
The Repository also holds a large collection of WTO Seattle material in the WTO Seattle Collection (Manuscript Collection 5177).
Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Economics and Banking; Seattle; Moving Images
- Brochures, flyers, articles, and newspapers related to protests, 1999-2001 (Box 1)
- AFL-CIO Workers' Rights and the World Trade Organization, undated (Box 1)
- Flyers, notes, maps, press contact list, and press releases, 1999 (Box 1)
- ACLU documents, reports, 2001 (Box 1)
- Map of protest route, undated (Box 1)
- The Citizens' Calendar, 1999 (Box 1)
- "Practicing what we Preach", 2001 (Box 1)
- Flyers, undated (Box 1)
- Local newspapers, 1999-2001 (Box 1)
- "Blind Spot" newsletter and WTO rally information, 1999 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, newsletters, notes, flyers, and pamphlets, 1999-2003 (Box 1)
- Buisness cards, flyers, correspondence, police complaint forms, and other WTO reports, articles, 2000 (Box 1)
- Notes, brochures, articles, flyers, and notes, approximately 1999 (Box 1)
- Binder: WTO filming logs and notes, approximately 1999 (Box 1)
- Notes, approximately 1999 (Box 1)
- 13 video tapes on WTO protests, other protests, other labor topics, and interviews, approximately 1999-2000 (Box 1)
- 69 mini DV cassettes, mostly of protests, many of WTO protests, and possibly interviews, approximately 1999 (Box 1)
- Newspapers, 1999 (Box 2)
- WTO Protest Poster, 1999 (Folder:oversize OS Folder)